export const Questions = [
    {
        question: "how much cost each episode of breaking bad ?  ",
        option1: "3M$",
        option2: "600k$",
        option3: "0",
        option4: "1 000M$",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the longest tv show to watch ?",
        option1: "friends",
        option2: "lost",
        option3: "plus belle la vie ",
        option4: "simpsons",
        answer:"4"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the dad in malcolm ?",
        option1: "Hal",
        option2: "Malcolm",
        option3: "Dewis",
        option4: "Frankie",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the fast food chain in Breaking bad",
        option1: "KFC",
        option2: "Los Pollos Hermanos",
        option3: "Mc Donald",
        option4: "Chicken Food",
        answer:"2"
    },
    {
        question: "Most popular netflix tv show in 2020",
        option1: "Casa de Papel",
        option2: "Bridgeton",
        option3: "The Witcher",
        option4: "Stranger Thing",
        answer:"2"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is creating the TV show Lord Of the ring",
        option1: "Amazon",
        option2: "OCS",
        option3: "Disney+",
        option4: "Netflix",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question: "Anthony starr didn't played on which show?",
        option1: "the boys",
        option2: "Banshee",
        option3: "American Gothic",
        option4: "Big bang theory",
        answer:"4"
    },
    {
        question: "What food was the character Pac Man modeled after?",
        option1: "Burger",
        option2: "Pasta",
        option3: "Pizza",
        option4: "Soup",
        answer:"3"
    },
    {
        question: "Rami Malek did played in one of these shows, which one  ?",
        option1: "Mr Robot",
        option2: "Breaking Bad",
        option3: "Maniac",
        option4: "The OA",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question: "Name of the main characters Breaking bad",
        option1: "Jesse and Walter ",
        option2: "John and Hank",
        option3: "Sheldon and Cooper",
        option4: "Tyrion and Daenerys",
        answer:"2"
    },
]
export const QuizzName ="TV show"